http://www.lakemedicalimaging.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement - Lake Medical Imaging - The Villages, Florida
Skip to content
Call Us Today! (352) 787-5858
For Patients Scheduling & AppointmentsTransferring Your Prior Images is SimplePatient FormsPay Bill OnlineHealth Companion Patient PortalUpfront PricingParticipating Insurance ProvidersPatient SafetyPatient SurveyAdditional ResourcesContact UsFor Providers Physician Portal/PACSParticipating Insurance ProvidersSureScan MRI FormOnline FormPrintable Form (PDF)Careers
MENUMENUDiagnostic Imaging
Mammography & Breast ImagingCT ScansMRI ScansPET/CT Scans and Nuclear MedicineUltrasoundFluoroscopyX-RayDEXA (Bone Density Analysis)
Women’s Imaging
Mammography and Breast ImagingBreast Ultrasound/ABUSBreast MRISenoBright Contrast Enhanced MammographyGenetic Testing for Breast CancerImage Guided Breast BiopsyGalactogram/DuctogramPelvic UltrasoundHysterosalpingogramDEXA [Bone Density Analysis]
Interventional Radiology
Minimally Invasive Procedures
Venous Ablation / Varicose VeinsSclerotherapy/Spider VeinsImage-Guided Needle BiopsyParacentesis and ThoracentesisVertebral AugmentationPain Management
Hospital-Based Procedures
P.A.D./AtherectomyVascular Access Procedures/Port and PICC Line PlacementTransjugular Intrahepatic Portosystemic Shunt (TIPS)Catheter EmbolizationInferior Vena Cava Filter Placement/DVTThrombolytic TherapyBalloon Angioplasty (Percutaneous Transluminal Angioplasty) and Vascular StentingDiagnostic BiopsyVenous InterventionArterial InterventionBiliary InterventionGastrointestinal Intervention
Interventional Oncology
Tumor AblationCryoablationYttrium-90 Radio-EmbolizationPort Placement
Pain Management
Injections for Joint PainEpidural Steroid InjectionsSacroIliac Joint InjectionsNerve Root Blocks
Our PhysiciansLocations
Search for:
Diagnostic Imaging Mammography & Breast ImagingCT ScansMRI ScansPET/CT Scans and Nuclear MedicineUltrasoundFluoroscopyX-RayDEXA (Bone Density Analysis)Women’s Imaging Mammography and Breast ImagingBreast Ultrasound/ABUSBreast MRISenoBright Contrast Enhanced MammographyGenetic Testing for Breast CancerImage Guided Breast BiopsyGalactogram/DuctogramPelvic UltrasoundHysterosalpingogramDEXA [Bone Density Analysis]Interventional Radiology Minimally Invasive ProceduresVenous Ablation / Varicose VeinsSclerotherapy/Spider VeinsImage-Guided Needle BiopsyParacentesis and ThoracentesisVertebral AugmentationPain ManagementHospital-Based ProceduresP.A.D./AtherectomyVascular Access Procedures/Port and PICC Line PlacementTransjugular Intrahepatic Portosystemic Shunt (TIPS)Catheter EmbolizationInferior Vena Cava Filter Placement/DVTThrombolytic TherapyBalloon Angioplasty (Percutaneous Transluminal Angioplasty) and Vascular StentingDiagnostic BiopsyVenous InterventionArterial InterventionBiliary InterventionGastrointestinal InterventionInterventional Oncology Tumor AblationCryoablationYttrium-90 Radio-EmbolizationPort PlacementPain Management Injections for Joint PainEpidural Steroid InjectionsSacroIliac Joint InjectionsNerve Root BlocksOur PhysiciansLocations
Search for:
Privacy Statementlmiadmin2015-01-13T19:40:42-05:00
Lake Medical Imaging is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Lake Medical Imaging Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Lake Medical Imaging website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Lake Medical Imaging collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Lake Medical Imaging also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Lake Medical Imaging. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Lake Medical Imaging for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Lake Medical Imaging Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Lake Medical Imaging public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Lake Medical Imaging does not read any of your private online communications.
Lake Medical Imaging encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Lake Medical Imaging so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Lake Medical Imaging is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Lake Medical Imaging and Lake Medical Imaging family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Lake Medical Imaging collects and uses your personal information to operate the Lake Medical Imaging Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Lake Medical Imaging also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Lake Medical Imaging and its affiliates. Lake Medical Imaging may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Lake Medical Imaging does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Lake Medical Imaging may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Lake Medical Imaging may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Lake Medical Imaging, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Lake Medical Imaging does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Lake Medical Imaging keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Lake Medical Imaging, in order to determine what Lake Medical Imaging services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Lake Medical Imaging to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Lake Medical Imaging Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Lake Medical Imaging or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Lake Medical Imaging; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Lake Medical Imaging, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Lake Medical Imaging Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Lake Medical Imaging pages, or register with Lake Medical Imaging site or services, a cookie helps Lake Medical Imaging to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Lake Medical Imaging Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Lake Medical Imaging features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Lake Medical Imaging services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Lake Medical Imaging secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Lake Medical Imaging secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Lake Medical Imaging will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Lake Medical Imaging encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Lake Medical Imaging is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Lake Medical Imaging welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Lake Medical Imaging has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Lake Medical Imaging at info@lakemedicalimaging.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Information: (352) 787-5858
Scheduling: (352) 365-0777
Toll-free: (866) 365-0777
Scheduling Fax: (352) 787-4655
Contact Us
© Copyright
Lake Medical Imaging   |   All Rights Reserved
Go to Top
